A Guide to the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) records FA084
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC Microforms, J; 135 Reels
  - PICIC: Credits (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-05)
  - PICIC: Directors-Meetings (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-06-(01-04))
  - PICIC: Directors-Memoranda (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-06-(01-04))
  - PICIC: Finance (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-07-(01-21))
  - PICIC: Finance-Statements (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-07)
  - PICIC: Incorporation (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-08-(01-03))
  - PICIC: Legal (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-11-(01-02))
  - PCIC: Publicity (Box 5, Card 2058-19-(01-03))
  - PICIC: Property (Reel J-100)
  - PICIC: Reports-Annual (Reel J-100, Box 5, Card 2058-20-(01-04))
  - PKDC: Finance (Reel J-123, Box 5, Card 202-07-(01-05))
    PKDC (Parkville Development Corporation)
  - PKDC: Finance (Box 5, Card 202-11-01)
    Cards mislabeled as Legal.
  - PKDC: Legal (Reel J-123, Box 5, Card 202-11-01)
  - PKDC: Organization (Reel J-123, Box 5, Card 202-13)
  - PKDC: Property (Reel J-123, Box 5, Card 202-17)
  - PKDC: Bairoa: General (Reel J-92, Box 5, Card 202-00-(01-02))
  - PKDC: Velaquez (Puerto Rico): General (Reel J-60, Box 5, Card 202-00)
  - Plastics, Inc.: Akron, Ohio: General (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 105-00-(01-02))
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Directors (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 266-06)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Finance (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 266-07-(01-09))
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Finance-Disburse (Box 5, Card 266-07)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Finance-General Shopping (Box 5, Card 266-07-(01-02))
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Incorporation (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 266-08)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Planning-Drawing (Box 5, Card 266-14-01)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Planning-Presentation (Box 5, Card 266-14-01)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Planning-Renderings (Box 5, Card 266-14-01)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Property-Appraisals (Box 5, Card 266-17-01)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants A-Z (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 266-17)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Property-Theatres (Reel J-1, Box 5, Card 266-17)
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Feasibility (Box 5, Card 266-20-(01-05))
  - Plaza Carolina, Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Feasibility-Summers (Box 5, Card 266-20-(01-02))
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Directors (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-06-(01-05))
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Finance (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-07-(01-15))
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Incorporation (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-08-(01-02))
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Legal (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-11-(01-02))
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Publicity (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-19)
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Reports-Operations (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-20)
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Staff (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-22)
  - ProCafe: de Venezuela C. A.: Stockholders (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 320-23)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Competition (Reel J-5, Box 5, Card 930-03)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Directors (Reel J-2, Box 5, Card 930-06-(01-06))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Directors-Board (Card 930-06-(01-05))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Finance (Reel J-2, Card 930-07-(01-66))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Finance (Reel J-3)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Finance-Exports (Card 930-07-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Incorporation (Reel J-4, Card 930-08-(01-03))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Insurance (Reel J-5, Card 930-09)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal (Reel J-4, Card 930-11-(01-14))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal-Decrees (Card 930-11-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal-Documents (Card 930-11-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal-Document "A" (Card 930-11-(01-03))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal-Document "B" (Card 930-11-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Legal-Document "C" (Card 930-11-(01-03))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Organization (Reel J-4, Card 930-13)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Planning (Card 930-14-(01-03))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Property-Equipment (Reel J-5, Card 930-17-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Publicity (Reel J-5, Card 930-19-(01-06))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Annual (Reel J-4, Card 930-20-(01-03))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1958 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1959 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1959 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1960 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1961 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1962 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1963 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1964 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1965 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1966 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1966 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1967 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1967 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1968 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1968 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1969 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1969 (Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1970 (Box 5, Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual - Spanish, 1970 (Box 5, Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Biannual, 1971 (Box 5, Card 930-20-01)
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Feasibility (Box 5, Card 930-20-(01-04))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Reports-Operations (Box 5, Card 930-20-(01-10))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Staff (Reel J-5, Card 930-22-(01-02))
  - Products de Cafe S. A.: El Salvador: Stockholders (Reel J-5, Card 930-23-(01-15))
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Credit (Reel J-5, Card 9901-05)
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Finance (Reel J-5, Card 9901-07-(01-04))
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Incorporation (Reel J-5, Card 9901-08-(01-02))
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Legal (Reel J-5, Card 9901-11)
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Legal-Documents (Card 9901-11)
  - Products of Asia, Inc.: New York: Publicity (Reel J-5, Card 9901-19)
  - Projects-Africa Coffee Soluble: Ivory Coast: General (Reel J-111, Card 9999-00-(01-08))
  - Projects-Africa Coffee Soluble: Ivory Coast: Reports (Reel J-111, Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Brazil Chemical Industry: General (Reel J-111, Card 9999-00-(01-04))
  - Projects-Brazil Chemical Industry: Reports (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Brazil Chemical Industry: Reports-IRI (IBEC Research Institute) (Reel J-111)
  - Projects-Brazil Coffee Soluble: General (Reel J-111, Card 9999-00-(01-51))
    9999-00-17, Two cards
  - Projects-Brazil Coffee Soluble: General (Reel J-112)
  - Projects-Brazil Coffee Soluble: Reports- Little, Arthur D. Incorporated (Reel J-112, Card 9999-20-(01-05))
  - Projects-Brazil Coffee Soluble: Reports-Tenco (Reel J-112, Card 9999-20)
  - Projects-Brazil Cold Storage: General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-Brazil Cold Storage: Reports (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Brazil Construction Materials-Wallboard-United States Wallboard Machinery Co.: General (Reel J-112, Card 9999-00-(01-23))
  - Projects-Brazil Construction Materials-Wallboard-United States Wallboard Machinery Co.: Reports (Reel J-112, Card 9999-20-(01-07))
  - Projects-Brazil Construction Materials-Wallboard-United States Wallboard Machinery Co.: Reports-Grace, W.R. & Company (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Brazil Construction Materials-Wallboard-United States Wallboard Machinery Co.: Reports-Siep, Donald R. (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-04))
  - Projects-Brazil-Fertilizers-Phosphates: General (Card 9999-00-(01-12))
  - Projects-Brazil-Fertilizers-Phosphates: Reports (Card 9999-20-(01-07))
  - Projects-Brazil-Grains-Rice: General (Reel J-113, Card 9999-00-(01-03))
  - Projects-Brazil-Grains-Rice: Reports (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Brazil-Marketing-Supermarkets: General (Reel J-113, Card 9999-00-(01-21))
  - Projects-Brazil-Marketing-Supermarkets: General (Reel J-114)
  - Projects-Brazil-Marketing-Supermarkets: Reports-Superettes do Leaozinho (Reel J-114, Card 9999-20-(01-04))
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: General (Reel J-113, Card 9999-00-(01-11))
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: Reports-Cust, Dante S. (Cusi) (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-05))
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: Reports-Palmgren, S.C. (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20)
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: Reports-Pictorial (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: Reports-SRI (Stanford Research Institute) (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-04))
  - Projects-Brazil-Oils, Vegetables-Babassu Nut: Reports-United States Vegetable Oil Mission to Brazil (Reel J-113, Card 9999-20-(01-04))
  - Projects-Brazil-Seeds, Vegetables: General (Reel J-114, Card 9999-00-(01-11))
  - Projects-Brazil-Seeds, Vegetables: Reports-Hanson, Lloyd C. (Reel J-114, Card 9999-20)
  - Projects-Central America (AM.) Marketing-Supermarkets: General (Reel J-114, Card 9999-00-(01-07))
  - Projects-Chile-Housing CAP: Finance (Reel J-45, Card 9999-07-(01-30))
    Housing CAP (Compania de Accrodel Pacifico, S. A.)
  - Projects-Chile-Housing CAP: Finance (Reel J-46)
  - Projects-Chile-Housing CAP: Legal (Reel J-46, Card 9999-11-(01-03))
  - Projects-Chile-Housing CAP: Staff (Reel J-46, Card 9999-22)
  - Projects-Chile-Marketing-Supermarkets: General (Reel J-114, Card 9999-00-(01-03))
  - Projects-Chile-Mining: General (Reel J-114, Card 9999-00-(01-15))
  - Projects-Chile-Mining: Legal-Laws (Reel J-114, Card 9999-11)
  - Projects-Chile-Mining: Planning-Plans (Card 9999-14-(01-02))
  - Projects-Chile-Mining: Reports (Reel J-114, Card 9999-20-(01-08))
  - Projects-Chile-Mining: Reports-Tower (Reel J-114, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Chile-Poultry: General (Reel J-115, Card 9999-00-(01-08))
  - Projects-Chile-Poultry: Reports (Reel J-115, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Colombia-Marketing-Supermarkets: General (Reel J-115, Card 9999-00-(01-09))
  - Projects-Colombia-Mining: General (Reel J-115, Card 9999-00-(01-13))
  - Projects-Colombia-Mining: Reports (Reel J-115, Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects- Colombia-Slaughterhouse: General (Reel J-115, Card 9999-00-(01-06))
  - Projects- Colombia-Slaughterhouse: General (Reel J-116)
  - Projects- Colombia-Slaughterhouse (Card 9999-00-(04-05))
  - Projects- Colombia-Slaughterhouse: Reports (Reel J-116, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Domestic-Enzymes: General (Card 9999-00-(01-07))
  - Projects-Domestic-Housing: Kentucky: Market Research Report (Card 924-16)
  - Projects-Domestic-Investments Hydroponics: General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-Domestic-Investments Sea Ponics Inc.: General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-Greece-Investment-Funds, Mutual: General (Reel J-116, Card 9999-00-(01-05))
  - Projects-Greece-Investment-Funds, Mutual: Legal (Reel J-116, Card 9999-11)
  - Projects-Iran Poultry: Directors (Reel J-129, Card 9999-06)
  - Projects-Iran Poultry: Finance (Reel J-129, Card 9999-07-(01-06))
  - Projects-Iran Poultry: Public Relations (Reel J-129, Card 9999-18-(01-03))
  - Projects-Iran Poultry: Staff (Reel J-129, Card 9999-22)
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: General (Card 9999-00-(01-07))
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: Brochure (Card 9999-20-01)
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: Reports-Fish Protein Con (Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: Reports-Fish Flour (Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: Reports-Fishery By-Product (Card 9999-20-01)
  - Projects-Latin America Fish Flour Viobin: Reports-Memo to IBEC (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Mexico Investment Funds, Mutual: General (Reel J-116, Card 9999-00-(01-06))
  - Projects-Mexico Investment Funds, Mutual: Legal (Reel J-116, Card 9999-11)
  - Projects-Mexico Investment Funds, Mutual: Reports (Reel J-116)
  - Projects-Mexico Marketing Supermarkets: General (Card 9999-00-(01-16))
  - Projects-Mexico Marketing Supermarkets: Reports (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Mexico Mining Fluorspar.-Samuels, L.: General (Card 9999-00-(01-03))
  - Projects-Offshore Insurance: General (Card 9999-00-01)
  - Projects-Peru-Milk: General (Card 9999-00-(01-15))
  - Projects-Peru-Milk: Plusa-General (Card 9999-00-(01-04))
  - Projects-Peru-Milk: Property-Equipment-Packaging (Card 9999-17-(01-02))
  - Projects-Peru-Milk: Sterile-Upl, etc.-General (Card 9999-00-(01-11))
  - Projects-Puerto Rico-Agriculture: General (Card 9999-00-(01-06))
  - Projects-Puerto Rico-Agriculture: Reports-Soybean Plant by Anderson Division (Card 9999-20-01)
  - Projects-Puerto Rico-Agriculture: Reports-Soybean Plant by Crouzet, J. G. (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Puerto Rico-Bagasse: General (Card 9999-00-(01-04))
  - Projects-Puerto Rico-Real Estate El Monte: Redevelop (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-Venezuela- Housing: General (Card 9999-00-(01-03))
  - Projects-Venezuela- Housing: Reports (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Venezuela- Housing: Reports-By Beach, Philip E. Jr (Card 9999-20-01)
  - Projects-Venezuela- Housing: Reports-San Luis Valencia-Crouzet (Card 9999-20-(01-03))
  - Projects-Venezuela- Housing-VBEC: Program-General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Investment Funds, Mutual: General (Reel J-116, Card 9999-00-(01-07))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Milk Reconstituted-Lactuaria del Caribe C.A.: General (Reel J-116, Card 9999-00-(01-33))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Milk Reconstituted-Lactuaria del Caribe C.A.: General (Reel J-117, Card 9999-00-(01-33))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Milk Reconstituted-Lactuaria del Caribe C.A.: Reports (Reel J-117, Card 9999-20-(01-02))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Mining: Credit (Reel J-118, Card 9999-05)
  - Projects-Venezuela-Mining: Finance-Disbursements (Reel J-118, Card 9999-07)
  - Projects-Venezuela-Mining: General (Reel J-117, Card 9999-00-(01-51))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Mining: General (Reel J-118, Card 9999-00-(01-51))
  - Projects-Venezuela-Oil Mendoza Syndicate: General (Card 9999-00-(01-07))
  - Projects-West Indies- Housing-Ariguanabo: General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Projects-West Indies- Housing-Caribbean Study: General (Card 9999-00-(01-02))
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Capital Stock-Prospectus (Reel J-109, Card 1522-02)
    Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc. (CIA Cervecerade Puerto Rico, Inc.)
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Directors (Reel J-109, Card 1522-06-(01-05))
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Finance (Reel J-109, Card 1522-07-(01-15))
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Insurance (Reel J-109, Card 1522-09)
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Legal (Reel J-109, Card 1522-11-(01-02))
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Legal-Huber, Karl (Reel J-109, Card 1522-11-(01-03))
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Publicity (Reel J-109, Card 1522-19)
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Annual Etc (Quarterly) (Reel J-109, Card 1522-20)
  - Puerto Rico Brewing Company Inc.: Puerto Rico: Staff (Reel J-109, Card 1522-22)
  - Ravica: Venezuela: Directors (Reel J-5, Card 835-06)
    Ravica (Reproductora Avicola, S. A.)
  - Ravica: Venezuela: Finance (Reel J-5, Card 835-07-(01-08))
  - Ravica: Venezuela: Legal (Reel J-5, Card 835-11-(01-02))
  - Ravica: Venezuela: Staff (Reel J-5, Card 853-22)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Directors (Card 927-06-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Finance (Card 927-07-(01-05))
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Insurance (Card 927-09-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Legal (Card 927-11-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Project-Operation Breakthrough (Card 927-16-(01-03))
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Public Relations (Card 927-18-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Publicity (Card 927-19-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Publicity-Brochure (Card 927-19-01)
  - Relbec Corp.: Puerto Rico: Reports-Feasibility (Card 927-20-01)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Finance (Card 9910-07-(01-04))
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Tenants (Reel J-5, Card 9910-17-(01-02))
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Banco Credito (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Benhil (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Franklin (Card 9910-17-(01-02))
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Gelpi (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Grand Union (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Guzman A. (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-IBEC & IRC (Card 9910-17-(01-02))
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Kresge (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tentants-Mueb. Ade (Card 9910-17)
  - Reparto Metropolitano (Shopping Center): Puerto Rico: Property-Tenants-Woolworth (Card 9910-17)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund: General (Card 9952-00-(01-02))
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc. (RBI): General (Reel J-6, Card 9954-00)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Inc. (RBI): Reports-Annual (Reel J-6, Card 9954-20-(01-04))
  - Rockefeller, David: General (Reel J-6, Card 9951-00)
  - Rockefeller Foundation: General (Reel J-6, Card 9953-00)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.: General (Reel J-6, Card 9950-00-(01-06))
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.: Property (Reel J-6, Card 9950-17-(01-02))
  - Rodopa: Finance (Reel J-6, Card 9902-07-(01-05))
  - Rodopa: Legal (Reel J-6, Card 9902-11-(01-02))
  - Rodopa: Publicity (Reel J-6, Card 9902-19)
  - Roi-Et Silk Mills Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-6, Card 503-06)
  - Roi-Et Silk Mills Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-6, Card 503-07-(01-11))
  - Roi-Et Silk Mills Ltd.: Finance-Aid-Guarantees (Card 503-07)
  - Roi-Et Silk Mills Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-6, Card 503-11)
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Competition (Reel J-8, Card 1407-03)
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Directors (Reel J-8, Card 1407-06-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Finance (Reel J-8, Card 1407-07-(01-10))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Incorporation (Reel J-8, Card 1407-08-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Legal (Reel J-8, Card 1407-11-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Planning (Reel J-8, Card 1407-14)
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Publicity (Reel J-8, Card 1407-19)
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Reports (Reel J-8, Card 1407-20-(01-04))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Reports-Annual (Card 1407-20-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Staff (Reel J-8, Card 1407-22-(01-04))
  - ROLIBEC Consultores de Seguros (Ca.-Ven.): Venezuela: Stockholders (Reel J-8, Card 1407-23)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Competition (Reel J-8, Card 432-03)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Directors (Reel J-8, Card 432-06-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Finance (Reel J-8, Card 432-07-(01-16))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Legal (Reel J-8, Card 432-11-(01-04))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Planning (Reel J-8, Card 432-14)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Publicity (Reel J-8, Card 432-19)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Reports (Reel J-8, Card 432-20)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Staff (Reel J-8, Card 432-22)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Stockholders (Reel J-8, Card 432-23)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Illinois: Stockholders-RBH (Card 432-23-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Peru: Finance (Reel J-8, Card 438-07-(01-04))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Peru: Legal (Reel J-8, Card 438-11-(01-03))
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Peru: Public Relations (Reel J-8, Card 438-18)
  - ROLIBEC Inc.: Peru: Staff (Reel J-8, Card 438-22)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Hong Kong Branch: Finance (Reel J-9, Card 435-07-(01-03))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Finance (Reel J-8, Card 434-07-(01-15))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Finance (Reel J-9)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Legal (Reel J-9, Card 434-11)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Publicity (Reel J-9, Card 434-19)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Reports (Reel J-9, Card 434-20)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Reports-Feasibility (Card 434-20-(01-03))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Staff (Reel J-9, Card 434-22)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Japan Branch: Staff-Aurell Est. (Card 434-22-(01-03))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Korea Branch: Finance (Reel J-9, Card 437-07-(01-04))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Korea Branch: Services (Reel J-9, Card 437-21)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Directors (Reel J-9, Card 433-06)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Finance (Reel J-9, Card 433-07-(01-09))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Incorporation (Reel J-9, Card 433-08)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Legal (Reel J-9, Card 433-11-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Organization (Reel J-9, Card 433-13)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Planning-European Division (Reel J-9, Card 433-14)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Planning-Okinawa (Card 433-14)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Planning-Philippine (Card 433-14-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Planning-Vietnam (Card 433-14)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Reports (Reel J-9, Card 433-20-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Staff (Reel J-9, Card 433-22)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Pan.: Stockholders (Reel J-9, Card 433-23)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Thailand Branch: Finance (Reel J-10, Card T433-07-(01-06))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Thailand Branch: Finance-Credit Advices (Card T433-07-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Thailand Branch: Legal (Reel J-10, Card T433-11)
  - ROLIBEC International Ltd. S. A.: Thailand Branch: Staff (Reel J-10, Card T433-22)
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Directors (Reel J-9, Card 436-06)
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Finance (Reel J-9, Card 436-07-(01-11))
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Finance-Disbursements (Card 436-07)
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Legal (Reel J-9, Card 436-11-(01-02))
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Planning (Reel J-9, Card 436-14)
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Publicity (Reel J-9, Card 436-19)
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Reports (Reel J-9, Card 436-20-(01-03))
  - ROLIBEC International (Thai) Ltd.: Reports-Annual (Card 436-20)